he knew no one would ever
come looking for him.
Do you want subtitles for any video?
-=[ ai.OpenSubtitles.com ]=-
40 HOURS AFTER EXPOSURE
Pay now. or nothing.
I pay you next week. I promise.
No money - you get nothing.
Fucking prawn. this isn't charity.
Hello. I'd like to buy
some meat. please.
Hey. a man!
Yes. have you got a hamburger.
or a steak roll?
Does it look like
a hamburger shop?
Which one do you want? Goat?
Come on. come on.
I don't have the whole day.
Is that a cat food there?
-Yeah. yeah. it is.
I'll have some of that. guys.
Fuck. man!
Hello. hello?
Baby is that you? Tania?
God. please let it be you.
Yes. it's me.
I'm so happy you called me. baby.
Wikus. listen to me. -Okay.
I have something to say to you.
and it's not gonna be easy.
No. no. look... listen baby.
before you say anything...
Your father is working against me.
but he's lying to you.
I did not have sex
with one of these...
...fokkin' creatures. man!
I would never have any kind of
pornographic activity
with a fokkin' creature!
They say that you're becoming
one of them. I can't do this...
Baby please. don't give up on me.
Don't give up on me baby.
because I can...
I want to see you again. baby.
I'm gonna fix my arm
and I'm gonna see you again.
and I'm gonna kiss you
and I'm gonna hold you again.
I also want you
to hold me again.
Baby?
Hey! Hey man!
Okay...
We are on tracking
directly to the location.
Roger that. I'll send you a
couple of choppers for backup.
You!
What do you want?
Come in. control. there is
our target moving to 66.
-You have to go.
-Please. I need your help.
We're gonna play hide and seek.
-Yes! Yes! -No. get back.
You want me to hide? Show me
your favorite hiding place.
Please. just go.
Leave us alone.
No. please. I need to hide.
They wanna kill me.
I just need to hide in here.
sir. for 5 minutes. okay?
What is this?
What are you doing here?
I remember you. -Nothing.
You must hide somewhere else.
Sir... please sir.
you have to help me.
I'm losing blood.
they're trying to kill me.
Only one thing that could
make that happen...
Quick! We have to hide him.
Now you... get down there.
Where's the fluid?
What did you do with it?
-Please!
-You took it...
I don't know what
you're talking about!
...I know you did.
I can see what's happening to you.
Tell me where it is.
Alright. alright.
Was it a black fluid
in a flask container?
Yes. that's it. Yes!
I confiscated it and
the guys at the lab took it.
It will be at the MNU.
MNU has it.
What is this?
-You ruined everything.
-Where is this?
Is that your shack?
This whole thing
is under your shack?
For 20 years you've...
had this fokking' thing in here?
Jesus. this is very illegal.
I mean. this is a find. you know.
I wish they catch you with this.
Fuel goes in here.
That's enough! Quiet!
Then we fly away.
I said quiet!
We cannot trust him.
What is he saying about the fuel?
Are you trying to start this thing?
Are you little fuckers trying
to start this and get away?
Never mind.
Yeah. you sneaky fokkin' prawns.
Too bad. I could've fixed you.
What? What did you say...
about the fixing?
What do you mean
you could fix me?
Forget it.
It doesn't matter. it's too late.
No. listen! Listen.
Are you saying that you can...
turn this prawn hand
into a human hand?
You can make me human again?
We have medical machines on the
mothership that can fix you. Yes.
We can use this ship
to fly up there.
That's fantastic!
You guys are brilliant!
I always thought that prawns
were intelligent. Let's do it.
I don't have fluid.
I could fix you and I could fly away.
But I don't have fluid.
Right. okay.
All right. I tell you what.
Why don't we...
go risk it some more?
Let's go collect some up.
It took twenty years
to collect that amount.
Fuck. man! Fuck!
Fuck! The only one that exists
is the one I confiscated?
Yes.
It's four stories underground.
Why does he keep looking at me
like that? -He likes you.
We are the same.
We're not the same.
We're not the fokkin' same.
There is a way out of this.
We get the fluid back from MNU.
Yeah. and what then?
Then we both die. eh?
Both of us dead.
That's a suicide mission. man.
Can you not fill my head
with that sort of nonsense?
The transformation is accelerating.
You don't have much time.
56 HOURS AFTER EXPOSURE
Fuck! Fuck! Fuck!
Hello.
-Wikus?
-Tania! Baby...
-Are you okay?
-Oh God! Thank God...
Where are you?
I'am...
It's not like my father said.
I know he was lying to protect me.
I just don't know
what to believe anymore.
Baby I know. but listen to me.
It's all lies. I swear to you.
Everything he said to you is lies.
-I know.
-What? What?
I believe you. Wikus.
I just want you back.
I want everything back
the way it was.
That's... baby. that's what I want.
That's great!
That's great news.
I can make it the way it was.
If you take me back.
How? How can we go back?
I have a plan.
I know how to fix it.
I know how to fix myself.
And it will be me.
And we'll be back together.
-You promise me?
-I promise you. baby.
Don't give up on me. okay?
Because I haven't
given up on you. All right?
I won't.
-I love you.
-I love you too.
Tell me you got a fix on him.
-D9.
How many moons
does our planet have?
Seven.
This planet only has one.
I can't wait to see our planet.
It's bigger than this one. isn't it?
Enough.
We go home now?
Not home. No.
This is where we must go.
See that tent there?
That might be ours.
I want to go home!
We can't go home.
Not anymore.
Hi. you don't wanna go to the tents.
they are not better.
They're smaller than the shacks.
Actually. more like
a concentration camp.
If I can get you that black fluid.
what happens then?
We go up to the mothership.
And you can start that thing?
-Yes.
Okay. so just to be clear:
this is gonna go back...
This is gonna go back
to human like this.
I can go home
and then you can go home.
You can take your boy.
you can take all the prawns.
if I can get you that fluid. right?
You said it was a suicide mission.
Maybe you were right.
We have no weapons.
They'll shoot us on sight.
Look. look... Christopher...
I know where we can get weapons.
Hi guys. Hello.
I would like to buy
some weapons. please.
How did you do this like that?
A doggie style with the demon.
I love it!
One brave white man. eh?
Were you wearing a condom?
I need to buy weapons. please.
You and I both know that there
are illegal weapons inside here.
I have money and I would like
to buy some of those...
Sit!
Thank you sir for your time.
Thank you very much for seeing me.
I would like to buy some weapons.
AK-47. some grenades...
maybe tear gas canisters.
I see you have limpet mines
here aswell. and I..
also see you guys have alien
weapons there. which is great!
If I could have one or two of those.
I have money. okay?
Now. I'm...
Sir! Please. sir!
I've heard about you.
Where do you have it?
Show me!
Oh. shit!
Come here. Come.
No. no... don't please!
Why are you doing this?
What do you want?
Shut up!
Forget the weapons!
I want the arm. Cut it off.
What is he saying?
I'll show you.
Holy shit!
You tell them to stand down!
You tell them to be quiet!
To back off!
Tell them to put the fokkin'
weapons in the bag!
Give me the fokkin' weapons. man!
Don't you. sir. look at me.
I said don't fokkin' look at me!
How did you get that hand?
Fokkin' hurry up there!
Look at me when I fuckin' speak
to you. What is your secret?
What did you do? Tell me!
I want that fuckin' arm.
What the fuck did you do?
You fuckin' mazungo.
I'm coming for you!
I'm coming for you and
I'm gonna get you!
Drop your fokkin' knife.
Drop your fokkin' knife!
He's useless to us dead.
-Would you relax?
For fuck's sakes. my men have
done this a hundred times before.
Maintaining a visual
on the location.
It's gonna be quick.
It's gonna be clean.
Best of all.
it's gonna be quiet.
Van De Merwe hasn't got a clue
what's coming his way.
It's empty!
-Where are they?
Target is gone.
The place is empty.
What do you mean. empty?
Where the fuck is he?
That little shithead has got
no idea what is coming his way.
I'm gonna find him.
There are the guards! At the gate!
Watch the guards at the gate. man!
Move! Get out!
They're going down.
Four stories down.
This is alien weaponry.
Give me a status report.
It's Van De Merwe.
He's on level four.
Switch to live. and
then we're taking him out.
Colonel. we weren't allowed
to use live ammunition.
They want him alive.
Stay here until I call you.
-I understand.
I need to get the door open.
No! I said stay until I call you!
Fuck!
I thought you said
not to kill them?
He shot at me!
Fuck! Get out!
Don't fuckin' look at me!
Get out!
Get the fuck out!
Everybody get the fuck out!
Get out! Go!
Move the fuck out! Go!
What is this place?
-Don't worry about that.
What do they do in here?
Check these boxes.
Any type of a box that looks like
it can hold a tube. Just check it out!
These fuckers!
Go. go. go...
Clear.
I got it! I got it!
Chris. I got it. Let's go!
Christopher!
Oh. fuck!
Listen... I promise you.
I didn't know they were doing this.
Until they brought me here
the other day.
I swear to you I did not know
they were doing this to you guys.
But Christopher...
look at me. Listen to me.
We need to leave now. Okay?
The whole of MNU
is gonna come down here.
He's going to destroy us.
We can do this. okay?
We're gonna get out of here...
Fire!
Move. move!
Shoot at the prawn!
Christopher!
What the fuck are you doing?
Think of your boy.
for fuck sake!
What the hell are you doing?
Are you out of your fuckin' mind?
You're gonna get us killed!
-What do we do now?
I thought you had a way out?
I didn't say anything
about the way out.
I promised you that we'll get in.
We're in! -I have an idea.
-Where are you going?
-Follow me!
What are you doing?
-Making a bomb.
Let's go!
Quick! Get in!
Go! Drive!
Okay!
Okay. hold on!
Fuck!
Reports are coming in of explosion
in downtown Johannesburg.
Well. there was a terrorist attack.
but I can assure you that we
dealt with it. Everything is fine.
Droop it down!
Droop it down! Decline!
They are really
close to us now!
Shit!
Let's go. let's go!
Don't drop that fokkin' thing!
Come on. move!
Get down there!
Go down and initiate
the binary commands.
Set it down right now!
When we get up to the mothership.
how long is this gonna take?
-To do what?
-The fixing. To fix me.
It's going to take a bit
longer than I thought.
Okay. that's fine.
How long do you need?
Three years.
Sorry. just go slowly
with the clicks there.
it sounded like you said
"three years". like human years.
Yes. Three years.
What? Three fuckin' years?
I will fix you.
but first I must save my people.
The deal was:
you go home. I get fixed!
I will not let my people
be medical experiments!
I'm a fokkin' medical experiment!
You hear me. Christopher?
I'm a fokkin' medical
experiment. man!
I must go home and get help.
I must use all the fluid
to travel quickly.
I'll just stay here. Christopher?
I'll just stay here in this shack.
And I'll see you in three years time?
-I will come back. I promise.
Christopher!
Where the fuck is he?
Hey. you're hiding Wikus
down there. my boy?
-Father?
-No. no. no.
Your daddy needs to stay here
to sort out a few things. alright?
We're gonna go. We're gonna
come back and fetch him. okay?
In here? -In there.
-Goes in here?
How the fuck do you
open this. prawn?
Father.
Show me. you fucker.
You want me to fuckin' kill you?
Is that what you fuckin' want. eh?
Right... there's no buttons.
On!
Activate?
My teachers teach only:
One prawn. one bullet.
I can't believe
I get paid to do this.
I love watching you prawns die.
Fuck. man!
Father!
Get out! Get out!
This is remarkable.
It looks like something is
emerging from the ground.
Something is definitely
coming out of the ground.
Okay... steady!
Go sit down.
I can't play with ya now.
Uncle Wikus is flying.
Bug off. Bug off!
Lock the weapon at target!
Fire when locked.
It seems to be drifting towards
the center of the territory.
We have a lock on him. -Fire!
Something is fired upon...
it has been hit!
What the fuck is that?
One of the engines is billowing
smoke. it's out of control.
It's going down. boss. Should I
send the boys to fuck him up?
Now... it hit the ground.
the massive impact.
and it's come to a standstill.
My son!
My son's in there!
Shut the fuck up!
Get this fucker inside.
We're moving out.
Come. let's go. let's go...
Move!
We're banking around now. trying
to get a better view of the ship
which is absolutely wrecked.
waiting for some of the smoke to clear.
Somebody has been
brought out of the vehicle.
It looks like a human being.
We are getting unconfirmed
reports that this might be
Wikus Van De Merwe. a fugitive
that has been on the run
from MNU for the past 3 days.
They are loading him into
a vehicle now. and heading off.
72 HOURS AFTER EXPOSURE
What the fuck?
We caught him. boss.
-Bring him to me.
Come on! Get back!
Oh. fuck!
Control. we're taking enemy fire!
We need support. Backup. now!
Fuck off! Fuck off. man!
Get you hands off me!
Fuckin' get off me!
Get your fuckin' hands off me!
Didn't I tell you...
that I'm gonna get you?
You came in here and you left
with something that belongs to me.
Fuck you.
Fuck you all!
I told you that
the day will come.
You've been running
around with my prize.
All I want is to eat that hand
and become like you.
No! It won't work...
Once I have that power.
no one will stop me.
It was your turn...
now it's mine!
Fighting MNU security forces.
this armed faction is doomed...
Now I'm gonna eat. my friend.
We're getting reports claiming that
the alien device is activating...
You see that prawn
back in the Casper? -Yeah.
He knows what the fuck
is up with that ship.
Get that fucker out
and get him talking. now.
Three contractors are closing in
on the nigerian compound. and...
Come. alien!
What's your plan?
How are you doing it?
Who's moving that ship?
All right. that's very clever.
Wait for my command.
Make sure you fuckin' shoot to kill.
Fuck! Move it! Move it!
Bring that fucker down!
Hold you fire! Hold your fire
and keep your positions!
It's Van De Merwe.
Hey. Dickus!
I'll come back for prawn.
alright guys?
Do you hear me. now?
-Run. Wikus!
-You hear me?
-Run!
And keep on running.
you fuckin' coward!
Run! Run!
Get the air support up.
and get on his fuckin' trail. now!
It's not gonna work. boss.
He's a tough one.
He's not gonna talk.
-Then just fuckin' kill him.
Fuck!
He's a tough one.
He's not gonna talk.
Then just fuckin' kill him.
Hey. c'mon. Get up!
I'm gonna get you out of here.
-I can't... it's too far.
-It's not too fokkin' far. Get up!
I'm gonna get you there.
I'm gonna get you to your boy!
C'mon. stay behind me!
Go back!
Run. run. run!
Arriving at the location now.
We have a clearance to engage.
Prawns are coming.
get down. get down!
They are headed for a drop site.
Knock these fuckers off!
Come to mommy. come...
Fuck!
Shit!
Are you hurt?
We can make it.
I was shot in the arm.
We can make it. come on!
Listen. you go ahead.
You can make it.
I'm gonna just... hold them
off here. and I'll join you soon.
No. we stick together.
I'm not leaving you here.
Take your boy and go home.
You have to make it.
Don't make me go through
all of this and not make it.
Do you understand?
-I will come back for you.
Go! Go now before
I change my mind! Go!
Three years. I promise.
I'm not fuckin' scared of you!
Quit fuckin' with me!
You want me?
Is that all you got?
Is that all you fuckin' got?
Some kind of quite extraordinary
light from the mothership.
I've never seen anything like it.
It's a beam of light...
Full scan. Okay.
Fire!
Get to the vehicle. now! Get going.
-Yes colonel. -Go. go. go!
Fuck!
Quit playing with me. Koobus!
You fucker!
Go. Chris. go.
Go home.
We go home now?
Yes.
74 HOURS AFTER EXPOSURE
Unbelievable.
Now I know why everybody
wants a piece of you.
I can't wait for those
med boys to cut you up.
But you know what?
You're not gonna waste
any more of my time.
You half-breed piece of shit!
I'm gonna just fuckin'
kill you myself.
Stay back. you fuck!
Stay back!
The people everywhere
across Johannesburg
are flooding the streets and
pouring out of their offices
and all eyes are pointed up towards
the sky on this momentous day.
It's the first time. ladies and
gentlemen. in over two decades.
that the mothership has shown
any sign of movement.
and people are
tremendously excited.
The city had come
to an absolute standstill.
Everybody wants to know
what's going to happen next.
There's no way of knowing whether
or not Christopher Johnson will return.
We don't know if
he was simply escaping.
whether he will
effect a rescue plan...
...and. as the so called
free press says.
whether or not he will come back
and declare a war on us.
This is the last known footage
of Wikus Van De Merwe.
And we can only speculate
as to what has happened to him.
The more zany conspiracy
theories state that
he's been captured by MNU
or by another government.
Or by perhaps some
shady government agency
and he's actually
being held in captivity.
If we knew where he was.
we would try and help him.
and that is the most difficult part.
not knowing where he is.
Wikus. sadly. is gone but
I'm the one who stays behind
with all the questions.
I can't give the answers.
He died in my mind a long
time ago. And that's that.
Wikus Van Der Merwe is a name
that will become very widely known
because of this pivotal role
that he played in this whole event.
He was an honest man. and he didn't
deserve any of what happened to him.
I mean. I know. I looked into a
computer system and I found stuff.
I mean. the whole data
was there. you know?
They didn't even do
a good job of hiding it.
Fundiswa Mhlanga is
currently awaiting trial
for exposing MNU's illegal
genetic research program.
District 9 was demolished
after the alien resettlement
operation was completed.
District 10 now houses 2.5 million
aliens and continues to grow...
You guys haven't seen a picture of
my wife. Let me show you my wife.
She's my special angel.
She even looks like an angel
with veil. you want to see that?
Look. you see.
with the white veil over the...
she even looks like an angel.
Everyone says that his wife is angel.
but this is a real angel that you
see there. on the cameras.
They won't put that
in the video. I don't think.
I found this at my front door.
As though somebody had
just left it there.
My friends say that
I should throw it away.
cause it's just a piece of rubbish.
That it couldn't possibly
come from him.
I know it's true.
Transcript AP
Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm